<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PRM391x_TourGuide_FX05543</string>
    <string name="location_title">HCMC, Vietnam</string>
    <string name="hotel_title">Khách sạn</string>
    <string name="atm_title">ATM</string>
    <string name="hospital_title">Bệnh viện</string>
    <string name="bus_title">Xe Bus</string>

    <string name="hotel_01">Vinpearl Luxury Landmark 81</string>
    <string name="hotel_01_address">720A Điện Biên Phủ Phường 22, Quận Bình Thạnh, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_02">Lotte Hotel Saigon</string>
    <string name="hotel_02_address">2A - 4A Tôn Đức Thắng, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 70000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_03">Park Hyatt Sài Gòn</string>
    <string name="hotel_03_address">Số 2 Công Trường Lam Sơn, Phường Bến Nghé, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 70000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_04">Hotel Nikko Saigon</string>
    <string name="hotel_04_address">235 Nguyễn Văn Cừ, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_05">Pullman Saigon Centre</string>
    <string name="hotel_05_address">148 Trần Hưng Đạo Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_06">Hotel des Arts Saigon Mgallery</string>
    <string name="hotel_06_address">76-78 Nguyễn Thị Minh Khai, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_07">Sofitel Sài Gòn Plaza</string>
    <string name="hotel_07_address">17 Lê Duẩn, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 70000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_08">Khách sạn Caravelle Sài Gòn</string>
    <string name="hotel_08_address">19-23 Công Trường Lam Sơn, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_09">Khách sạn New World Sài Gòn</string>
    <string name="hotel_09_address">76 Lê Lai, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 70000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hotel_10">Mia Saigon Luxury Boutique Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel_10_address">2-4 Đường số 10, phường An Phú, Quận 2, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>

    <string name="atm_01">ATM OCB Hội Sở</string>
    <string name="atm_01_address">45 Lê Duẩn, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_02">ATM OCB Hân Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_02_address">65 Nguyễn Du, Phường Bến Nghé, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_03">ATM OCB PGD Kinh Tế</string>
    <string name="atm_03_address">135 Trần Hưng Đạo, Phường Cầu Ông Lãnh, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_04">ATM OCB Vincom Center</string>
    <string name="atm_04_address">72 Lê Thánh Tôn, Phường Bến Nghé, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_05">ATM OCB PGD Nguyễn Thái Bình</string>
    <string name="atm_05_address">194 Nguyễn Công Trứ, Phường Nguyễn Thái Bình, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_06">ATM OCB Đại học Kiến Trúc</string>
    <string name="atm_06_address">196 Pasteur, Phường 6, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_07">ATM OCB PGD Phạm Ngọc Thạch</string>
    <string name="atm_07_address">17 Phạm Ngọc Thạch, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_08">ATM OCB Cao Ốc 123-127</string>
    <string name="atm_08_address">123 - 127 Võ Văn Tần, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_09">ATM OCB Trương Định</string>
    <string name="atm_09_address">24C Trương ĐỊnh, Phường 6, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="atm_10">ATM OCB Quận 4</string>
    <string name="atm_10_address">39-41 Hoàng Diệu, Phường 12, Quận 4, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>

    <string name="hospital_01">Bệnh Viện 175</string>
    <string name="hospital_01_address">782 Nguyễn Kiệm, Quận Gò Vấp, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_02">Bệnh Viện 30 tháng 4</string>
    <string name="hospital_02_address">9 Sư Vạn Hạnh, Phường 9, Quận 5, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_03">Bệnh Viện An Bình</string>
    <string name="hospital_03_address">146 An Bình, Phường 7, Quận 5, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_04">Bệnh Viện An Sinh</string>
    <string name="hospital_04_address">10 Trần Huy Liệu, Phường 12, Quận Phú Nhuận, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_05">Bệnh Viện Bệnh Nhiệt đới</string>
    <string name="hospital_05_address">190 Bến Hàm Tử, Phường 1, Quận 5, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_06">Bệnh Viện Bình Dân</string>
    <string name="hospital_06_address">371 Điện Biên Phủ, Phường 4, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_07">Bệnh Viện Chấn thương Chỉnh hình</string>
    <string name="hospital_07_address">929 Trần Hưng Đạo, Phường 1, Quận 5, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_08">Bệnh Viện Chợ Rẫy</string>
    <string name="hospital_08_address">201B Nguyễn Chí Thanh, Quận 5, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_09">Bệnh Viện Đa Khoa Hoàn Mỹ</string>
    <string name="hospital_09_address">124 Trần Quốc Thảo, Phường 7, Quận 3, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>
    <string name="hospital_10">Bệnh Viện Đa Khoa Sài Gòn</string>
    <string name="hospital_10_address">125 Lê Lợi, Phường Bến Thành, Quận 1, Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh 700000 Việt Nam</string>

    <string name="bus_01">Tuyến 01</string>
    <string name="bus_01_destination">Bến Thành – Bến xe Chợ Lớn</string>
    <string name="bus_02">Tuyến 02</string>
    <string name="bus_02_destination">Bến xe buýt Sài Gòn - Bến xe Miền Tây</string>
    <string name="bus_03">Tuyến 03</string>
    <string name="bus_03_destination">Bến xe buýt Sài Gòn - Bến xe buýt Thạnh Lộcn</string>
    <string name="bus_04">Tuyến 04</string>
    <string name="bus_04_destination">Bến xe buýt Sài Gòn- Cộng Hòa - Bến xe An Sương</string>
    <string name="bus_05">Tuyến 05</string>
    <string name="bus_05_destination">Bến Xe Chợ Lớn – Biên Hòa</string>
    <string name="bus_06">Tuyến 06</string>
    <string name="bus_06_destination">Bến xe Chợ Lớn – Đại học Nông Lâm</string>
    <string name="bus_07">Tuyến 07</string>
    <string name="bus_07_destination">Bến xe Chợ Lớn – Gò Vấp</string>
    <string name="bus_08">Tuyến 08</string>
    <string name="bus_08_destination">Bến xe Quận 8 – Đại học Quốc gia</string>
    <string name="bus_09">Tuyến 09</string>
    <string name="bus_09_destination">Bến xe buýt Chợ Lớn - Bình Chánh - Hưng Long</string>
    <string name="bus_10">Tuyến 10</string>
    <string name="bus_10_destination">Đại học Quốc gia – Bến xe Miền Tây</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>